

Contact

manarajhar93@gmail.com

+971-50-988-7983

Sharjah, United Arab Emirates

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/manar-

https://yimmy456.github.io/

https://github.com/Yimmy456

Skills

- Unity
- **Unreal Engine**
- Visual Studio
- Photoshop
- Dreamweaver
- C++
- C#
- Java
- Python
- **HTML**
- CSS
- **JavaScript**
- **Gameplay Programming**
- **UI Programming**
- Al Programming
- **AR Programming**
- **VR Programming**
- **Tools Programming**
- **Physics Programming**
- iOS and Android Development
- PC Development
- 3D Math Skills
- Communication Skills
- Problem-Solving Skills

Languages

- English
- Arabic

Manar Ajhar

Game Developer | Software Engineer | Multimedia Editor

Summary

Skilled software engineer with 10+ years of experience in software programming. Very proficient in using C#, C++, Java, and Visual Studio. Other acquired skills include augmented reality (AR) programming, artificial intelligence (AI) programming, user interface (UI) programming and tools development. Capable of developing apps using AR and AI.

Experience

Educational Game for Asthmatic Children October 2023 - Present

Developing a game for smartphones using Unity to educate children about asthma. The game utilized Augmented Reality.

Mobile Game Application

January 2018 - August 2018

Developed a multiplayer game for iPhone X with a team. The game had Augmented Reality and Networking.

First-Person Shooter Game

September 2015 - May 2016

Developed a First-Person Shooter game for PCs using Unity. The game had Al elements.

Additional Experience

July 2015 – Newcastle Upon Newcastle Intern August 2015 University Tyne, England, UK

I was an intern as part of my program during my bachelor's. I learned about how to develop games using Construct 2 and Unreal Engine 4.

Education

University of Sharjah

September 2021 – June 2023 Queen's University

Kingston, Ontario, Canada Master's Degree GPA: 3.50 / 4.00

September 2017 - October 2018 Sheridan College

Oakville, Ontario, Canada Post-Grad Certificate GPA: 3.18 / 4.00

September 2013 – January 2017

Sharjah, the United Arab Emirates Bachelor's Degree GPA: 3.23 / 4.00